#### **Andri Suryono**

Klaten, Jawa Tengah | Portofolio | Linkedin | +6285878183521 | andri.jobs06@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a graduate of Informatics Engineering and have experience as an IT staff in garment manufacturing for 5 years. I just finished a course at Eduwork with the Mern Stack class. In my previous workplace, I used to create or develop programs with the PHP programming language and My SQL database by successfully creating a Production Garment System program for production data manage. Currently, I am open to working in the positions of Full Stack Developer, Backend Developer, and Front End Developer.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**Eduwork** Yogyakarta

Full Stack Mern - (Intership Project)

*August 2023 - October 2023* 

- Developed a full stack food store application and achieved 80% feature completion rate in 15 days, using MERN stack (MongoDB, Express Js, React, Node Js).
- Designed databases for products, users, addresses, carts, invoices, categories with 90% accuracy. and orders within 7 days by using MongoDb and Mongoose ODM for efficient data storage.
- Implemented secure user authentication and authorization, reducing unauthorized access using JWT, bcrypt
- Create a news aplication with live search feature and integration with News API with 90% accuracy rate within 2 days. Tools used: React, React Bootrsrap.
- Create a Hijja Store Home Page from the specified ui/ux list and integrate from the systemtoko.com API in less than 7 days. Tools used: React, React Bootstrap, Axios.

## PT. Sinar Klaten Makmur

Klaten, Central Java

IT Staff - (Contract)

April 2022 - July 2023

- Developed Packing-Shipment Scan System for validation feature to minimise user error The result is 90% as requested by management with additional custom reports.
- Create a system design for the Garment Production Application, by creating a system design, to create a mysql table and divide it into several stages of coding.
- Completed the 1st stage of coding the creation of the Bundle Record System, with the print out of Bundle records and ticket bundles by the system. With the exact same appearance that has been running before.
- Completed the 2nd stage of coding the production output scan system. The result makes the production data management can directly pull the system data by scanning the barcode on the ticket bundle scanned by each department process beforehand.
- Completed the final stage of coding, customising reports and adding modules, the result is a user-friendly system, through which production data can be directly pulled from the system.
- Implementation to users of the new IT Inventory Beacukai system, the result is that users when confused or have problems can be handled directly. By training and assisting the input process directly.

#### PT. FGX INDONESIA

Klaten, Central Java

IT Staff - (Contract)

October 2020 - March 2022

- Create a system design for the Packing-Shipment Barcode Scan Application, by creating a system design, to table design (Create Relational database) and dividing it into several coding stages.
- Completed the first phase of the Packing-Shipment Coding System, to minimise operator barcode paste errors, by adding specified validation extras.
- Complete the final stage of Coding Packing-Shipment System, namely, to process output data, stock data, balance order shipment, generate packinglist shipment by creating costom reports according to user and management requests.
- Design and ensure the development of custom IT Inventory & Accounting Systems to Vendors for new companies in accordance with user & management requests. By liaising and communicating between users and vendors.
- Configuring the network and dimikrotik to make the connection more stable, and creating remote server access and cctv and vpn, by adding dynamic indihome ip to the network settings.

## **CERTIFICATION & BOOTCAMP**

# **MERN STACK**

Agustus 2023 – Oktober 2023

- Creation of a Git repository to manage project source code and learn best practices in collaborative software development.
- Learn Framework ReactJS for building user interfaces.
- Learn to make HTTP requests to the server, which is useful for communicating with the backend with a JavaScript library using Axios
- Learn for creating application servers using Node.js as a JavaScript server-side runtime and Express.js as a web framework
- Learn to manage and interact with databases with sequelize on MySQL and Mongoose on MongoDB

## **EDUCATION**

# Universitas Widya Dharma

Klaten, Central Java

S1 - Teknik Informatika GPA 3.4 September 2013 – October 2017

- Undergraduate Thesis: Academic Information System Using Php at Mts N Srebegan
- I learnt Web programming languages from HTML, CSS, PHP, Javascript and learnt MY SQL database which supported my work at my old workplace.

## SKILLS, INTERESTS, & LANGUAGES

**Technical Skills:** React.js | Node.js | Express.js | My SQL | MongoDB | HTML | CSS | Javascript | PHP | Bootstrap | Tailwindcss | Restfull API | Git | Postman

 $\textbf{Soft Skills:} \ \ Time \ Management \ | \ Problem \ Solving \ | \ Team \ Work \ | \ Helpfulness \ | \ Critical$ 

Thinking | Emotional Intelligence | Inovatif | Communication

**Interests:** Full Stack Developer, Backend Developer, Front End Developer **Language:** Indonesian (Native), English (Beginner), Javanesse (Native)

#### **PROJECTS**

Point Of Sale
Sept

2023

Details: A system that can support sales transactions, purchases, product management and

transaction reports digitally.

Tools: React.JS, Node JS, Express JS MongoDB, CSS Boostrap

Link : https://github.com/andry06/project-eduwork

Demo:-

# **Production Garment System**

July 2022 - June

2023

Details: A system that supports the management of garment production data from order data recap, pre-production, bundle record system, monitoring production output and stock of goods in each department from cutting to the finishgood process, and there is a shipment process to generate packinglist of finished goods that are sent.

Running: PT. Sinar Klaten Makmur

Tools : PHP, Javascript, HTML, CSS Bootstrap

Link : Demo :-

#### REFERENCE

Name : Ringga Gustavino

Company : Eduwork

Position : Mentor - Mern Stack

Contact : 081296001282